Inventaris van het archief van de Stichting World Press Photo, 1955 - 2009
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- PUBLICATIEARCHIEF, A.
  - Jaarboeken World Press Photo., 1962-2009; 1-170; 172 delen
    - World Press Photo JAARBOEK 1995, 79
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu Publishers, The Hague.Design: Hans van Blommestein, Louis Voogt. ISBN 90-12-08193-9. Size: 132 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo YEARBOOK 1995, 80
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London. ISBN 0-500-97418-7. Size: 132 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo ALBUM 1995, 81
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-7165-0974-4. Size: 132 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo JAHRBUCH 1995, 82
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87258-005-1. Size: 132 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo ANNUARIO 1995, 83
      Spanish. Publisher: Omnicon, Madrid. ISBN 84-88914-02-4. Size: 132 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo JAARBOEK 1996, 84
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu Publishers, The Hague.Design: Hans van Blommestein, Louis Voogt. ISBN 90-12-08303-b. Size: 132 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo YEARBOOK 1996, 85
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 0-500-97436-5. Size: 132 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo ALBUM 1996, 86
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-7165-1033-5. Size: 132 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo JAHRBUCH 1996, 87
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87258-007-8. Size: 132 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo LIBRO DELL’ANNO 1996, 88
      Italian. Publisher: Contrasto, Milano. ISBN 0-500-974365. Size: 132 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo ANNUARIO 1996, 89
      Spanish. Publisher: Omnicon, Madrid. ISBN 84-88914-05-9. Size: 132 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo JAARBOEK 1997, 90
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu/ Standaard, Den Haag/ Antwerpen.Design: Hans van Blommestein, Louis Voogt. ISBN 90-75-56636-0. Size: 140 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo YEARBOOK 1997, 91
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 0-500-97449-7. Size: 140 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo ALBUM 1997, 92
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-1765-1062-9. Size: 140 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo JAHRBUCH 1997, 93
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87258-008-6. Size: 140 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo ANNUARIO 1997, 94
      Spanish. Publisher: Omnicon, Madrid. ISBN 84-88914-06-7. Size: 140 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 1998, 95
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu/ Standaard, Den Haag/ Antwerpen.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 90-75-56660-3. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 1998, 96
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 0-500-97464-0. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 1998, 97
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-7165-1113-7. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 1998, 98
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87258-009-4. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 1998, 99
      Italian. Publisher: Contrasto, Milano. ISBN 88-86982-08-9. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 1998, 100
      Spanish. Publisher: Omnicon, Madrid. ISBN 84-88914-08-3. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 1999, 101
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu/ Standaard, Den Haag/ Antwerpen.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 90-57970-25-2. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 1999, 102
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 0-500-97478-0. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 1999, 103
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-7165-1182-X. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 1999, 104
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87258-010-8. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 1999, 105
      Spanish. Publisher: World Press Photo, Amsterdam. ISBN 90-12-08723-6. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2000, 106
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu/ Standaard, Den Haag/ Antwerpen.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 90-57970-76-7. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2000, 107
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 0-500-97486-1. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2000, 108
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-7165-1210-9. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2000, 109
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87258-011-6. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2000, 110
      Polish. Publisher: Gazeta Wyborcza, Poznan. ISBN 83-907350-5-9. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2000, 111
      Spanish. Publisher: World Press Photo, Amsterdam. ISBN -. Size: 148 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2001, 112
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu Publishers, The Hague.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 90-12-08995-6. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2001, 113
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 0-500-97598-1. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2001, 114
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-7165-1238-9. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2001, 115
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87258-012-4. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2001, 116
      Italian. Publisher: Contrasto Due, Roma. ISBN 88-86982-26-7. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2001, 117
      Polish. Publisher: Gazeta Wyborcza, Poznan. ISBN 83-907350-7-5. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2001, 118
      Spanish. Publisher: World Press Photo, Amsterdam. ISBN -. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2002, 119
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu Publishers, The Hague.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 90-12-09484-4. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2002, 120
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 0-500-97614-7. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2002, 121
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-7165-1261-3. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2002, 122
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87258-013-2. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2002, 123
      Italian. Publisher: Contrasto Due, Roma. ISBN 88-86982-55-0. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2002, 124
      Polish. Publisher: Gazeta Wyborcza, Poznan. ISBN 83-907350-8-3. Size: 152 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 2002, 125
    - World Press Photo 03, 126
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu Publishers, The Hague.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 90-12-09781-9. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 03, 127
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 0-500-97623-6. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 03, 128
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-7165-1302-4. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 03, 129
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87268-014-0. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 03, 130
      Italian. Publisher: Contrasto Due, Roma. ISBN 88-86982-82-8. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 03, 131
      Polish. Publisher: Gazeta Wyborcza, Poznan. ISBN 83-916961-5-4. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 03, 132
      Spanish. Publisher: World Press Photo, Amsterdam. ISBN -. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 04, 133
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu Publishers, The Hague.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 90-12-09974-9. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 04, 134
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 0-500-97633-3. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 04, 135
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-7165-1342-3. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 04, 136
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87258-015-9. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 04, 137
      Italian. Publisher: Contrasto Due, Roma. ISBN 88-89032-23-5. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 04, 138
      Polish. Publisher: Gazeta Wyborcza, Poznan. ISBN 83-916961-6-2. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 04, 139
    - World Press Photo 05, 140
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu Publishers, The Hague.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 90-12-10618-4. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 05, 141
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 0-500-97645-7. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 05, 142
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-7165-1383-0. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 05, 143
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87258-016-7. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 05, 144
      Italian. Publisher: Contrasto Due, Roma. ISBN 88-89032-74-X. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 05, 145
      Polish. Publisher: Gazeta Wyborcza, Poznan. ISBN 83-916961-7-0. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 05, 146
    - World Press Photo 06, 147
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu Publishers, The Hague.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 90-12-11057-2. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 06, 148
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 0-500-97497-7. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 06, 149
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 3-7165-1434-9. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 06, 150
      German. Publisher: GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf. ISBN 3-87258-017-5. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 06, 151
      Italian. Publisher: Contrasto Due, Roma. ISBN 88-6965-022-7. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 06, 152
    - World Press Photo 07, 153
      Dutch. Publisher: Sdu Publishers, The Hague.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 978-90-12-11889-7. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 07, 154
      English. Publisher: Thames & Hudson, London, New York. ISBN 978-0-500-97667-8. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 07, 155
      French. Publisher: Editions Benteli, Berne. ISBN 978-3-716-51480-1. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 07, 156
      German. Publisher: GFW PhotoPublishing GmbH, Düsseldorf. ISBN 978-3-87258-018-4. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 07, 157
      Italian. Publisher: Contrasto Due, Roma. ISBN 978-88-6965-065-9. Size: 156 pp., A4 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 07, 158
    - World Press Photo 08, 159
      Dutch. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Uitgevers, Amsterdam.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 978-90-5330-614-7. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 08, 160
      English. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Publishers, Amsterdam. ISBN 978-90-5330-621-5. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23
    - World Press Photo 08, 161
      French. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Publishers, Amsterdam. ISBN 978-90-5330-624-6. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23
    - World Press Photo 08, 162
      German. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Publishers, Amsterdam. ISBN 978-90-5330-622-2. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23
    - World Press Photo 08, 163
      Italian. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Publishers, Amsterdam. ISBN 978-90-5330-623-9. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23
    - World Press Photo 08, 164
      Spanish. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Publishers, Amsterdam. ISBN 978-90-5330-625-3. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23
    - World Press Photo 09, 165
      Dutch. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Uitgevers, Amsterdam; Lannoo Uitgeverij, Tielt, Belgium.Design: Heijdens Karwei. ISBN 978-94-900-4801-3; NUR 653. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23 cm paperback.
    - World Press Photo 09, 166
      English. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Publishers, Amsterdam. ISBN 978-90-5330-677-2. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23
    - World Press Photo 09, 167
      French. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Publishers, Amsterdam. ISBN 978-90-5330-679-6. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23
    - World Press Photo 09, 168
      German. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Publishers, Amsterdam. ISBN 978-90-5330-678-9. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23
    - World Press Photo 09, 169
      Italian. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Publishers, Amsterdam. ISBN 978-90-5330-680-2. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23
    - World Press Photo 09, 170
      Spanish. Publisher: Mets & Schilt Publishers, Amsterdam. ISBN 978-90-5330-681-9. Size: 160 pp., 29,7 x 23
  - Retrospectieve publicaties., 1979-2006; 171-201; 31 delen
    - Világesemények képekben, 1979, 171
      Hungarian. Author, producer: A képeket válogatta; Keleti Ëva; A kötetet tervezte Mészáros Károly. Publisher: (c) 1979 World Press Photo Holland Foundation; (c) 1979 Képzömüvészeti Alap Kiadóvállalata, Budapest. ISBN 963 336 167 2. Size: ? pp., 26,5x20,4 cm cm hardcover
    - Ooggetuige van het wereldnieuws 25 jaar World Press Photo’s, 1981, 172
      Dutch. Author, producer: Harold Evans, redactie; Ontwerp: Michael Rand en John Tennant. Publisher: (c) 1981 Stichting World Press Photo Holland (c); Teleboek BV, Amsterdam, The Netherlands. ISBN 90 6122 126 9. Size: 192 pp., 27,7x22,3 cm cm hardcover
    - Eyewitness 25 years through World Press Photos, 1981, 173
      English. Author, producer: Harold Evans, editor; Designed by Michael Rand and John Tennant. Publisher: (c) 1981 by World Press Photo Holland Foundation; Quiller Press Ltd., London. ISBN 0 907 62100 7. Size: 192 pp., 27,7x22,3 cm hardcover
    - Eyewitness 25 years through World Press Photos, 1981, 174
      English. Author, producer: Harold Evans, editor; Designed by Michael Rand and John Tennant. Publisher: (c) 1981 by World Press Photo Holland Foundation; William Morrow & Co. New York, USA. ISBN 0-668-00654-X; TR820.E846; 779’.990982; 81-9452. Size: 192 pp., 27,7x22,3 cm hardcover
    - Instants d’Années 25 ans de World Press Photo. Les 300 documents qui ont fait l’Événement, 1981, 175
      French. Author, producer: Projet conçu par Michael Rand et John Tennant. Légendes d’Harold Evans avec le concours de Neil Hepburn. Traduction en français de Philippe Bonnet. Responsable de la rédaction: Joop Swart. Publisher: (c) 1981 by World Press Photo Holland Foundation; (c) 1981Hachette Gamma Press, France. ISBN 2.01.008277.X; 26-51-0454-01; 26-0454-4; 81-IX. Size: 192 pp., 27x21,5 cm paperback
    - Testemunha Ocular 25 anos atraves das melhores fotos jornalisticas, 1981, 176
      Portuguese. Author, producer: Editor: Victor Civita; Tradução: Arlette Dialetachi B. Bastos. Publisher: (c) 1981 by World Press Photo Holland Foundation; (c) 1981 para a língua portuguesa: Livros Abril S.A. Cultural e Industrial, São Paolo, Brasil. ISBN -. Size: 224 pp., 27,7x22 cm hardcover
    - 25 Años World Press Photo 1956-1981 - 25 años a través de las mejores fotos de prensa del mundo, 1981, 177
      Spanish. Author, producer: Texto: Harold Evans; Disegño: Michael Rand y John Tennant. Publisher: (c) 1981 by World Press Photo Holland Foundation; Technipress, S.A. de Ediciones, Madrid. ISBN 84-300-4732-8; Depósito legal: M-30320-1981. Size: 200 pp., 27x21,5 cm paperback
    - Pressfoto! 1956-1980 25 Års Världsnyheter i Bild, 1981, 178
      Swedish. Author, producer: Text: Harold Evans; Bildredaktion: Michael Rand; Svenska pressklipp: Lars Lagerstedt Översättning: Hans Nygren. Publisher: (c) 1981 by World Press Photo Holland Foundation; Svenska dagbladet/ BonnierFakta Bokförlag AB. ISBN 91-34-48852-9. Size: 192 pp., 27,7x22 cm hardcover
    - Husker du…. 25 års pressebilleder fortæller verdenshistorie, 1982, 179
      Danish. Author, producer: Design: Michael Rand og John Tennant; Co-ordinerende udgiver: Joop Swart; Oversaettelse: Christian Dahlerup Koch. Publisher: (c) 1981 by World Press Photo Holland Foundation; (c) 1982 for Danmark: Forlaget Komma A/S København. ISBN 87-87837-09-0. Size: 192 pp., 27,7x22 cm hardcover
    - Eyewitness 25 years through World Press Photos, 1982, 180
      English. Author, producer: Harold Evans, editor. Publisher: 1982 Penguin Books, UK, USA, Australia, Canada, New Zealand. ISBN 0-14-00-6238-6. Size: 192 pp., 27x21,5 cm paperback
    - Eyewitness 2 - 3 Decades Through World Press Photos, 1985, 181
      English. Author, producer: Harold Evans, editor. Publisher: Quiller Press, London, UK. ISBN 0-907621-55-4. Size: 208 pp., 27,7x22 cm hardcover
    - Eyewitness 2 - 3 Decades Through World Press Photos, 1985, 182
      English. Author, producer: Harold Evans, editor. Publisher: This updated edition 1985; Second impression 1990.. Size: pp., 27,7x22 cm hardcover
    - Eyewitness 2 - 3 Decades Through World Press Photos, 1985, 183
      English. Author, producer: Harold Evans, editor. Publisher: Quiller Press, London, UK. ISBN 0-907621-55-4. Size: 208 pp., 27x21,5 cm paperback
    - Het Fotografische Geheugen - Twaalf kenners over persfotografie, 1987, 184
      Dutch. Author, producer: (c) 1987 Stichting World Press Photo, Amsterdam; Samengesteld door Emile Meijer en Joop Swart. Publisher: 1987 Nijgh & Van Ditmar, Amsterdam. ISBN 90 236 7811 7; NUGI 932. Size: 208 pp., 23x16 cm paperback
    - The Photographic Memory - Press photography – twelve insights, 1987, 185
      English. Author, producer: (c) 1987 Stichting World Press Photo, Amsterdam; Edited by Emile Meijer and Joop Swart. Publisher: 1988 Quiller Press, London, UK; Same with imprint: ‘Presented by Kodak’ ‘Admedia’. ISBN 1 870948 10 6. Size: 208 pp., 23,5x16,5 cm hardcover
    - Occhio Testimone - World Press Photo: trent’anni di storia, 1988, 186
      Italian. Author, producer: (Introduction by) Furio Colombo, A cura di Robert Pledge (editor). Publisher: 1988 Gruppo Editoriale Fabbri Bompiani, Sonzogno, Etas S.p.A., Milano, Italia. ISBN -. Size: 224 pp., 23x24 cm hardcover
    - World Press Photo 1956-1992, 1992, 187
      Japanese. Author, producer: Edited by Asahi Shimbun, Cultural Projects Division, Tokyo. Publisher: (c) 1992 World Press Photo Foundation, Amsterdam; (c) 1992 Asahi Shimbun, Tokyo. ISBN -. Size: 216 pp., A4 cm paperback
    - World Press Photo 1956-1995, 1995, 188
      Japanese and English. Author, producer: Edited by Asahi Shimbun, Cultural Projects Division, Tokyo. Publisher: (c) 1995 World Press Photo Foundation, Amsterdam; (c) 1995 Asahi Shimbun, Tokyo. ISBN -. Size: 232 pp., A4 cm paperback
    - Dit Kritisch Weerzien - Veertig Jaar World Press Photo, 1995, 189
      Dutch. Author, producer: Redactie Stephen Mayes. Publisher: (c) 1995 Stichting World Press Photo Holland; Sdu Publishers, The Hague, 1995. ISBN 90-12-08261-7. Size: 228 pp., 32x24,2 cm paperback
    - This Critical Mirror - 40 Years of World Press Photo, 190
      English. Author, producer: Editor Stephen Mayes. Publisher: (c) 1995 Stichting World Press Photo Holland; Thames & Hudson, London, New York, 1996. ISBN 0-500-27848-2; Libr. Congress 95-60603. Size: 228 pp., 32x24,2 cm paperback
    - Ce Mirroir Critique - Les 40 Ans de World Press Photo, 191
      French. Author, producer: Rédacteur Stephen Mayes. Publisher: (c) 1995 Stichting World Press Photo Holland; Benteli Verlag, Berne, 1995. ISBN 3-7165-0993-0. Size: 228 pp., 32x24,2 cm paperback
    - Der Spiegel Der Kritik - 40 Jahre World Press Photo, 192
      German. Author, producer: Herausgeber Stephen Mayes. Publisher: (c) 1995 Stichting World Press Photo Holland - GFW-Verlag, Düsseldorf, 1995. ISBN 3-87258-006-X. Size: 228 pp., 32x24,2 cm paperback
    - Este Critico Espejo - Los 40 Años de la World Press Photo, 193
      Spanish. Author, producer: Editor Stephen Mayes. Publisher: (c) 1995 Stichting World Press Photo Holland; Omnicón, Madrid, 1995. ISBN 84-88914-04-0. Size: 228 pp., 32x24,2 cm paperback
    - 50 jaar World Press Photo, 2005, 194
      Dutch. Author, producer: Sheet of Dutch postage stamps. Publisher: TPG Post, The Netherlands, issued 8 October 2005. ISBN Article 251061. Size: pp., 11x15
    - 50 jaar World Press Photo, 2005, 195
      Dutch. Author, producer: Tekst: Karin Engelbrecht en Rodney Bolt. Publisher: (c) 2005 Stichting World Press Photo, Amsterdam; Sdu Uitgevers, Den Haag. ISBN 90 12 10918 3; NUR 653. Size: 64 pp., 17,5x17,5 cm hardcover
    - Fifty Years World Press Photo, 196
      English. Author, producer: Text: Karin Engelbrecht and Rodney Bolt. Publisher: (c) 2005 Stichting World Press Photo, Amsterdam; Sdu Publishers, The Hague. ISBN 90 12 11063 7; NUR 653. Size: 64 pp., 17,5x17,5 cm hardcover
    - De Dingen Zoals Ze Zijn - 50 Jaar fotojournalistiek in context [World Press Photo 50], 2005, 197
      Dutch. Author, producer: Door Mary Panzer, met een nawoord van Christian Caujolle, idee en realisatie: Chris Boot. Publisher: (c) World Press Photo, 2005; Uitgegeven door Chris Boot Ltd., Londen; Informatie: Sdu Klantenservice, Den Haag. ISBN 90 12 10865 9; NUR 652. Size: 384 pp., 31x24 cm hardcover
    - Things As They Are - Photojournalism in context since 1955 [World Press Photo 50], 198
      English. Author, producer: By Mary Panzer. With an Afterword by Christian Caujolle; Chris Boot (editor). Publisher: (c) World Press Photo, 2005; Uitgegeven door Chris Boot Ltd., Londen; Distribution by Thames & Hudson, London. ISBN 0-9546894-5-3. Size: 384 pp., 31x24 cm hardcover
    - Things As They Are - Photojournalism in context since 1955 [World Press Photo 50], 199
      English. Author, producer: By Mary Panzer. With an Afterword by Christian Caujolle; Chris Boot (editor). Publisher: (c) World Press Photo, 2005; Uitgegeven door Chris Boot Ltd., Londen; Distribution by Thames & Hudson, London. ISBN 0-9546894-5-3. Size: 384 pp., 30x23,2 cm paperback
    - Things As They Are - Photojournalism in context since 1955 [Aperture/ World Press Photo], 200
      English. Author, producer: By Mary Panzer. With an Afterword by Christian Caujolle. Publisher: (c) World Press Photo 2005; First Aperture [New York] edition published in collaboration with Chris Boot and World Press Photo. ISBN 1-59711-014-0; Library of Congress: 2005931654. Size: 384 pp., 31x24 cm hardcover
    - Las cosas tal como son - El Fotoperiodismo en Contexto Desde 1955 [World Press Photo 50/ Blume], 2006, 201
      Spanish. Author, producer: Mary Panzer. Epílogo de Christian Caujolle. Publisher: (c) World Press Photo 2005; (c) 2006 Art Blume, S.L., Barcelona. ISBN 84-9801-135-3. Size: 384 pp., 30x23,2 cm paperback
  - Masterclass publicaties., 1994-2009; 202-218; 17 delen
    - Masterclass ’94 - Generation X, 1994, 202
      English. Exhibition: Netherlands Institute for Photography, Rotterdam, 16 Nov. – 11 December 1994. Publisher: Focus Publishing, Amsterdam. ISSN ISSN -. Size: 20 pp., 28,5x21,5 cm.
    - Joop Swart Masterclass ‘95 - Patriotism, 1995, 203
      English. Exhibition: Arti et Amicitiae, Amsterdam, 1– 5 November 1995. Publisher: Focus Publishing, Amsterdam. ISSN -. Size: 20 pp., 28,5x21,5 cm.
    - Joop Swart Masterclass ‘96 - Neighbours, 1996, 204
      English. Exhibition: Netherlands Institute for Photography, Rotterdam, 16 Nov. – 31 December 1996. Publisher: Special edition by De GeÏllustreerde Pers b.v.. Editors: Sytske Kiestra, Martijn Kramer. Design: Hans van Blommestein, Louis Voogt. ISSN -. Size: 24 pp., 34x25 cm.
    - Joop Swart Masterclass ‘97 - Friendship, 1997, 205
      English. Exhibition: Netherlands Institute for Photography, Rotterdam, 9 Nov. – 5 December 1997. Publisher: Special edition by De GeÏllustreerde Pers b.v.. Coordinator: Sytske Kiestra. Design: Hans van Blommestein, Rob van Assendelft. ISSN -. Size: 24 pp., 34x25 cm.